Guide to the Donald Oliver/Chelsea Music Archive, 1907-2008 (bulk 1962-1991) MSS.254
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Series III: Conductor Scores and Orchestrations
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn, "Papir iz Dokh Vays (Paper is White)", [1997] (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn, "Belz", [1997] (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn, "Titanik", [1997] (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Patinkin, Mandy/Mama-Loshn, "Der Alter Tsigayner (White Christmas)", [1997] (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Peter Pan Piano Conductor Score, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Peter Pan [Broadway and National Tour]/"Indian Dance and Tag", [1979] (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Peter Pan [Broadway]/"Hook's Scheme #2" Extension, August 20, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Peter Pan [Broadway]/"Indian Dance" [Revised], August 28, [1979] (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Peter Pan [Broadway]/"Tarantella Tag", 1979 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Peter Pan [Broadway]/"Wendy" New House and Ending, August 31, [1979] (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Peter Pan [Broadway]/"Hook's Waltz", [1979] (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Peter Pan [Broadway]/Opening Act II [Revised], August 30, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Peter Pan [Broadway]/"Lullaby" Extension, August 20, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Peter Pan [Broadway]/Finale Act III, August 20, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Peter Pan [Broadway]/Bows Parts 1 and 2, August 7, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Peter Pan [Broadway]/Exit Music, [1979] (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/ "Prologue", [1981] (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/"Danger Barking", [1981] (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/"I've Gotta Crow", [1981] (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/"Captain Hook", April 13, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/"Ugh-A-Wug", [1981] (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/ Entr'Acte, [1981] (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/ Act II Opening Revisions, [1981] (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/"Indian Dance" Revised, [1981] (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/"Wendy" Revisions, April 13, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/ "Wendy Tag" Revisions, April 13, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/"Cinderella Tag" Revisions, April 13, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/"Grow Up" Revisions, [1981] (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/"Hook Pours Poison" Revisions, [1981] (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/"Ugh-A-Wug Encore", [1981] (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/ Ship Opening Act III, [1981] (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Peter Pan National Tour/ Bows Revisions, April 13, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Peter Pan II Venture/"Mysterious Lady", February 9, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Peter Pan Miscellaneous Scores, undated (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Phantom [Kopit-Yeston Production], 1991 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Phantom of the Opera Act II, [1988] (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Platinum Scores, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"Beautiful Relationship, undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"Where's the Woman", undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"The Enemy is Man", undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"Free", undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"Fortune Cookie", undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"Love Bells", undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"Nothing Can Stand in the Way of Love", undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"Sweet Madness", undated (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"Good Humor Man", undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"S. Kleins", undated (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"Guava - Free Me", undated (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"Bring Back the Days", undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Ring-A-Levio/"Little Girl Lost", undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Ring-A-Levio/ Act II Finale, undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - 70, Girls, 70 Act I Piano Conductor Score, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - 70, Girls, 70 Act II Piano Conductor Score, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Shlomo Master Scores and Parts [1 of 2], [2008] (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Shlomo Master Scores and Parts [2 of 2], [2008] (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Shlomo/"Hashmieni Opening" (2), [2008] (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Shlomo/"Master of Prayer/Veyesoyu" (3), [2008] (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Shlomo/"Esa Enai (Small)" (4), [2008] (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Shlomo/"Waltz-Part 1 (My Little Nazi)" (5), April 11, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Shlomo/"Waltz - Part 2 (I Am the Police)" (5A), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Shlomo/"Waltz - Part 3 (Uh-Oh, There's a Nazi at the Door)" (5B), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Shlomo/"Bereishis" (6), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Shlomo/"Bereishis Playoff" (6A), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Shlomo/"Too Many Nazis/The Crakow Niggun" (7), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Shlomo/"Shomer Yisrael Ship" (8), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Shlomo/"After Shomer Ship" (7A), April 3, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Shlomo/"Keep the Fire Burning" (9), April 6, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Shlomo/"Torah Song" (10), April 5, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Shlomo/"Uforatzoh (Hide the Matzoh)" (11), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Shlomo/"Ruach" (13), April 3, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Shlomo/"Gospel Song" (14), April 3, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Shlomo/"Oh Sinnerman" (15), April 3, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Shlomo/"Bless My Album" (17), April 8, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Shlomo/"Od Yishama" (18), April 8, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Shlomo/"Shlomo Medley" (19), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Shlomo/"Esa Enai Sequence" (20), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Shlomo/"To All of My Brothers" (21), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Shlomo/"Song of Shabbos" (23), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Shlomo/"To Israel" (24), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Shlomo/"Adam Was Alone" (25), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Shlomo/"Return Again" (26), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Shlomo/"Shlomo's Final Concert" (27), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Shlomo/"Am Yisrael Chai" (28), [2008] (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Side by Side Piano I Act I, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Side by Side Piano I Act II, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Side by Side Piano II Act I, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Side by Side Piano II Act II, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Stevens, Marti [singer]/"London Pride" Score, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Twelfth Night - Shakespeare - Master Scores and Parts [1 of 2], undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Twelfth Night - Shakespeare - Master Scores and Parts [2 of 2], undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Ulysses Master Scores and Parts - Act I, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Ulysses Master Scores and Parts - Act II [1 of 2], 1974 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Ulysses Master Scores and Parts Act II [2 of 2], 1974 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - West Side Story/Katie Couric Cancer Benefit [Somewhere; One Hand One Heart], [2002] (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Woman of the Year Piano Conductor Score, May 31, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Zorba Piano Conductor Score, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 2)